Previously on
Two and a Half Men...
Oh, Charlie.
I would have given anything
to be like you.
Even for a day.
I'm Melanie.
Nice to meet you, Melanie.
I'm...
Charlie.
Charlie Harper.
Whoa. Look who's getting busy.
Hey.
He's acting like
my Uncle Charlie.
He's even dressing
like my Uncle Charlie.
People are really
worried about you.
The only reason people
are worried about me
is 'cause they can't wrap their
heads around how cool I am.
- I'm fine.
- What's your name?
- Charlie Harper.
- You're not fine.
I've got a great idea.
You and me, Vegas.
This doesn't look
like the Bellagio.
Uh, it's the, uh, back entrance.
Hello, Mr. Harper.
If you could,
just come with us.
Uh, don't forget my bags.
And we'll be going
to the presidential suite?
Oh, yes, sir.
Uh, I'm going to need
a bucket of ice,
a bottle of scotch
and two Asian hookers.
Yes. Thanks.
Winning.
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go,
Mr. Harper.
Now that you're leaving us,
you can have your belt
and shoelaces back.
Oh. Thank you.
But believe me,
there was never any possibility
I was going to hurt myself.
Yeah, well,
it only takes one whack job
hanging from the shower curtain
to ruin it for everybody.
I... I suppose.
And I guess I did lose it
for a little while there.
Lose it?
We had a pool on how
long it would take
to get you toilet
trained again.
Really?
Cost me 50 bucks.
And a pair of nice white shoes.
Sorry.
I tend to leak under pressure.
So you think
you're ready
to go back out
into the world?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
I mean, I've, uh,
learned a lot about myself
in the last month, and I...
I now have the tools
to deal with life
on life's terms.
You know, a lot of people
say that,
but you'd be surprised
how another couple of weeks
of treatment can make
all the difference in the world.
You have another pool,
don't you?
Nothing personal.
Just trying to get even.
Sorry I couldn't be more help.
That's okay.
Got $100 says you'll be back
before Christmas.
Thanks for your support.
You really want to thank me,
stop taking your medication.
Or double up.
Either way, I'll have
a happy holiday.
Hope you weren't planning
on leaving
before you give
your old buddy Gary a hug.
Of course not.
I love you.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x09 ♪
Frodo's Headshots
Original Air Date on November 14, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Thanks for picking me up.
No problem.
So you're not
crazy anymore?
I was never
actually crazy.
Then why were you
in the nuthouse?
It's not a nuthouse;
it's a stress clinic.
What's the difference?
About $2,500 a week.
But the good news
is that I got a lot out of it.
I mean, I am ready to deal
with whatever life
throws at me, you know.
Full speed ahead.
Well, that's good, 'cause
I've got something
I want to talk
to you about.
Oh, anything.
Dad's here for you, pal.
Cool.
So remember Megan?
Oh, yeah, that was, uh,
your little girlfriend.
Uh, she's seems
like a great gal.
Well, I'm glad
you like her
'cause she's
kind of pregnant.
Kind of?
She's not showing yet.
She's still in
her first semester.
Oh, my God.
How-how...
how did this happen?
I mean, what about
our talks about, uh,
sexual responsibility
and-and using protection?
I can explain that.
Go ahead.
I was drunk.
Okay. Okay.
I have the tools.
And how do you propose
to take care of this child?
Oh, we got that
figured out.
First, we're going to
quit school and get jobs.
Okay, stop right there.
What jobs?
Advertising-- we're going
to teach the baby to talk
and put him
in E-Trade commercials.
You're joking.
No. We figure the baby they got
is probably getting pretty old.
What does your mother
think about this?
- She doesn't know.
- What?
I was hoping
you'd tell her.
Why do I have to tell her?
Because she already hates you
and she scares the crap
out of me.
Hey, there he is.
Welcome home, buddy.
Thank you.
I'm glad to be here.
Yeah. How you feeling?
Fine. Why are you
whispering?
Oh, I don't want
to startle you.
Walden, I'm okay.
Yeah, sure you are.
Hey, Walden,
guess what.
I'm going to be a dad.
Really?
Wow.
How you feel about
that, Grandpa?
Well, it's, uh, not something
I would have chosen
for him at this stage
of his life,
but he will continue
to have my love and support.
If it's a boy,
we're going to name him Frodo.
You're not making it
easy for me, pal.
You should have
used a condom.
Or you should have.
Hey, look who's back
from the loony bin.
It wasn't a loony bin;
it's a stress clinic.
Did they let you
keep your belt?
Uh, well...
Loony bin.
- There's your mail.
- Thank you.
Hey, Berta,
I'm going to be a dad.
What's funny?
From where you're
standing, nothing.
Did you tell
him your news?
Mmm, it'll keep.
Hey, open your mail.
Okay. Let's see.
Uh, bill, bill, jury duty,
bill.
Ooh! Oh, here we go.
My refund from the IRS.
Ooh.
Whew!
Just in time
what with all these bills.
Might want to set some of that
aside for Frodo's headshots.
Huh.
It's not a refund at all.
I'm being audited.
What's so funny?
From where you're
standing, nothing.
I guess you're
probably wondering
why I asked you guys
to come over.
We understand, Alan.
Mental illness is nothing
to be ashamed of.
I'm not mentally ill.
It was a stress clinic.
Did the door lock from the
inside or the outside?
Uh, uh, well, the... the...
Nevertheless, the reason
I called a family meeting
is because, uh, Jake
and Megan
have some news.
Oh, my God.
She's pregnant.
Well, that was easy.
Who wants cake?
How could you do this?
She made me.
What?
Oh, come on.
Between the two of us,
who was a virgin?
Okay, okay.
What's done is done,
but if we can come
together as a family,
we can deal with this
without finger-pointing.
Your father's right.
Let's just calm down
and talk it through.
Is it just me,
or does Herb and Judith's kid
look a lot like Alan?
Well, you know,
there is a slight resemblance.
- Damn it, Jake!
- What the hell is wrong with you?
How could you be
so irresponsible?
I mean, what were you thinking?
What were you thinking?
Did we raise you not to know
any better than this?
What do you have
to say for yourself?
When are you going
to tell him your news?
Ah, I don't want to
make things worse.
See, that's the big difference
between you and me.
And you're a
grandpa now.
Grandpa. Grandpa.
A grandpa and grandma...
Hey.
Hey. How'd
your audit go?
It wasn't so much an audit
as a brutal prison rape
with a number two pencil.
I'm confused.
Did you like it or not?
They say I owe them $80,000.
So not.
But the good news is,
if they take
everything I own,
they'll only get four.
$4,000?
Four dollars.
But I'm not worried.
Because I have the tools to cope
with whatever life throws at me.
No, you don't.
Alan?
Oh, Lyndsey.
Sweetheart,
are you a sight for sore eyes.
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
Oh.
Alan, you're home.
Hey, Walden, I think now's
the time to tell him.
Tell me what?
Aw.
What's so funny?
From where I'm standing,
everything.
♪ Men. ♪
I'm sorry you had
to find out this way.
Oh. Really? Really?
How would you have liked me
to hear about it?
Twitter? Facebook?
A singing telegram?
♪ Ta-ra-ra boom-dee-ay,
I banged your girl today ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a billionaire,
I still have all my hair. ♪
I-I understand
that you're upset,
but you have to see this
from our viewpoint.
What's your viewpoint?
The sex is awesome.
It really is.
He's the best
I've ever had.
No, you're the best
You're
the best I've had.
- No, you.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
How did this happen?
It was actually
kind of a meet cute.
Uh, Lyndsey came here
to see where you were,
and I told her
where you were,
and then she started
to cry, and...
bippity-boppity-boo,
we're having sex.
Bippity-boppity-boo?
How do you go
from crying to sex?
With him, it was always
the other way around.
Okay, okay, and-and-and what
was the cute part?
Look at him.
No, look at you.
- No, you.
Hey! Hey! I'm still here!
I mean, how-how
could you do this?
How-how could you have an affair
while I'm locked up
in the booby hatch?
I thought it
was a stress clinic.
Everybody knows what it was!
I lost my freaking mind!
But luckily, now I'm better,
so I have the tools
to cope with whatever life
throws at me!
That's great, Alan,
'cause there's one more thing.
Oh, super. Let me have it.
- You need to move out.
- What?!
Come on, it'd be
creepy if you're
downstairs listening
while we're having sex.
Lyndsey doesn't make any noise.
I do now.
Fine. Fine.
Let me just get my things.
Uh, not necessary.
We packed your stuff.
Oh, yeah. It's all in a storage
bin out by the airport.
But don't worry, I took care
of the first month's rent.
Here's the key.
Why, thank you.
You know, I hope someday,
we can look back
at this as friends
and just laugh.
Someday?
Why wait? Let's laugh now.
Okay, I'll go.
That's it!
I am done being a doormat.
I'll show 'em.
I will show 'em all.
They won't have Alan Harper
to kick around anymore.
And they will be sorry.
Apologies will be made,
tears will be wept,
but it's all gonna be too late
'cause I am out of here!
Sleeping the big sleep,
the ol' dirt nap.
Adios, muchachos,
it's the last roundup.
God, check, please.
Perfect.
♪ Men. ♪
Hi! Hi, Mom, it's me!
I need a place to stay.
Walden kicked me out
and my car blew up
and I had to hitchhike
over here!
So, solly,
Missy Everyn no home.
Missy Everyn?!
Come on, Mom!
What are you doing?
Let me in!
I'm soaking wet,
and I had to give a truck driver
a happy ending just to get here!
Go away! I call po-rice!
What kind of accent is
that supposed to be?!
Herro? Po-rice?
Clazy man outside.
You come quick!
Fine, fine! I'm leaving!
Thanks a lot!
Rots of ruck!
Unbelievable.
Blindsided by my son...
reamed by the IRS...
rejected by my lover...
betrayed by my friend...
molested by a truck driver...
cast out by my mother...
and rained on by God.
And this isn't even the worst
week of my life.
Oh, come on.
Might as well make myself
comfortable.
Nowhere to go from here.
End of the line.
Rock bottom.
Can a man sink any lower?
Asked and answered.
Pardon me.
Do you happen
to have a flashlight?
Uh, what?
The light in my storage
unit isn't working.
I need a flashlight.
Oh. Uh, yeah, sure. Um...
Yeah, uh... what the hell?
Oh, here you go.
Thank you.
My fur coats all feel alike
in the dark.
Lot of things feel alike
Ooh, you rascal!
Uh, I'm Alan Harper.
Veronica Hastings.
Come here often?
No, but the night is young.
Ooh. Innuendo?
Not usually.
But if you play
your cards right...
Listen, Alan Harper,
I keep some nice wines
in my storage unit.
Can I interest you
in a glass?
I would like that very much.
Don't go away.
There is no chance
of that happening.
You had a plan all along,
didn't you, God?
Alan?
Yes, Lord?
Over here.
Oh! Oh, Herb.
What are you doing here?
I called Walden.
He told me this is where
I might find you.
Oh, well, I, uh, I appreciate
you stopping by,
but I'm not really set up
for entertaining yet.
I didn't just stop by.
I have some news for you.
Really? Good news?
I had a DNA test done on
my daughter Millie.
Oh?
Turns out she's your daughter.
Bad news.
And it's about to get worse.
Oh, come on!
Good-bye, Alan.
Oh, no, Herb, please, please!
I'm about get laid
by Jessica Rabbit!
No, Herb, no!
Oh, thank God
I'm still in the loony bin.
It's a stress clinic.
♪ Men. ♪
Thanks for picking me up.
No problem.
I'm surprised Walden let
you take his car.
I know, right?
With my driving record?
I'm really glad
you're feeling better.
You had me worried.
I'm sorry. Didn't mean to.
But everything's fine now.
Good.
Hey, is it too soon
to talk to you
about something important?
You can talk to me
about anything.
I have the tools to cope.
Cool. Remember Megan?
Oh, God...
Well, we've been
going out for a while now
and all of a sudden,
she's saying
she wants to see
other people,
but I want to keep it,
you know, monotonous.
That, that's it?
She's not pregnant?
No, of course not.
I've been stuck at third base
for months.
That's a relief.
For you, maybe.
Anyway, I was just
wondering if you had
some advice on how to keep
a woman from leaving you.
So how was
the food in there?
♪ Men. ♪
It feels strange
to be back here.
Just to warn you,
things are
a little bit different
than you remember them.
What do you mean?
I promised Walden
I wouldn't tell you.
- Bye.
- Where you going?
I'm gonna take Walden's car
over to Megan's,
see if it helps me
slide into home.
Wear protection!
I'm wearing it now!
Whoa.
Hey, buddy.
How ya doing?
I'm okay.
Good, good, I'm glad.
Walden, you don't have
to talk to me
like a crazy person.
Oh, crazy people
don't talk like this.
Regular people talk
like this when
they're talking
to crazy people.
Fine. Whatever.
I see you finished
redecorating.
Yeah.
What do you think?
Ah, it looks fantastic.
Oh, hey, check this out.
Computer, lights off.
Computer, music on.
♪ ♪
That's awesome.
Yeah, it's the home
of tomorrow.
Except it's today.
Computer, music off.
Okay, let me try.
Uh, computer, lights on.
Oh, no, that won't work.
It's keyed to my voice.
Oh, well, then how do I turn
the lights on and off?
You can't.
Hey, let me show you
the kitchen.
Boy, sure hope I can flush
the toilet.
♪ Ta-da! ♪
Ta-da, indeed.
Oh, hey, check this out.
I connected the refrigerator
to the Internet.
Ice.
Wait for it.
Is that cool or what?
And if I want ice?
You just call me and then
I'll call the refrigerator.
Oh, oh, check this out.
Computer, television on.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
What is it about
a giant TV?
Right? I mean, just looking
at it gives me a chubby.
Welcome home, buddy.
Oh, thanks, Walden,
but you and I both know
this is not my home.
Oh, sure, it is.
No, let me finish.
I had a lot of time
to think while I was away.
At least after I came off
the thorazine.
And I realized that it's one
thing to live off my brother,
but he's gone and...
now his stuff's gone, too.
I really don't belong
here anymore.
So you're moving out?
Oh, no, no! God, no!
I mean, look at
the size of this thing.
No, I just want
you to know that
I'm aware of the
absurdity of our situation.
Bring it in.
Oh...
Computer, music on.
♪ And I will always
love you... ♪
And let me know if you need ice.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==